[English subtitles are available]
[Song Of The Moon]
[Episode 09]
How can we make this tree,
which has been dead for 10,000 years,
bloom in five days?
Should we first figure out
how this tree died?
This tree was originally planted by
our Demon King and Demon Queen.
They nourished the tree with their love.
There were thousands of Water Hyacinths
blooming on this tree at that time,
which was very spectacular.
Water Hyacinth?
Is it the flower
engraved on your flute?
Yep.
Since then,
Water Hyacinths
have become the mark of our Melody race.
The one engraved on my flute
is just a simple pattern.
The real Water Hyacinth
has the same blue-purple color
as the one on my clothes.
Then
why did this tree die?
Later, the Demon King and Demon Queen turned against each other.
And the Demon Queen committed suicide and died.
The tree has gradually withered
since then,
and those Water Hyacinths have never appeared again.
The Demon King and Demon Queen turned against each other.
Why would that happen?
It's a long story.
I'll start with their encounter.
Thousands of years ago,
the Demon King disguised this place as a residence of the immortals.
And he disguised himself as a lake fairy to pursue Immortal Ze Shui.
A demon and a fairy
have fallen in love
ever since.
And they planted the Brahma tree together.
Immortal Ze Shui often played Bone-Corroding Harp under the tree
to help the tree grow.
The sapling, irrigated by her love
and energized by her magic,
sprouted in three days,
grew into a tree in seven,
and blossomed in ten.
Wasn't Immortal Ze Shui
the sister of the God of the Moonlight?
A love that begined with deception like this
would surely cause problems later, right?
You're right.
Immortal Ze Shui found out the truth.
Then they had a dispute.
Ze Shui tried to leave.
But the Demon King sealed her divine spirit and imprisoned her.
And all those eventually led to her death.
After that, the God of the Moonlight cursed our Melody race
after discovering the tragic death of Immortal Ze Shui.
Since then,
we have never been able to leave the water.
And the Brahma tree withered
and died.
But,
since they loved each other, why couldn't they be together?
Lu Li.
Yes?
You've only had one glass of rouge wine,
how come you're already drunk?
I'm going to get him a hangover cure.
I'll go with you.
Don't go.
Okay.
I'll stay with you.
Then... I'll just stay here.
Don't look at him. Look at me.
Why can't I look at him?
My heart hurts
if you look at him.
It hurts so much.
It's more painful than being poisoned.
Does it hurt?
Are you drunk or have you become stupid?
Neither.
But my heart tells me
that I want to be like this
for the rest of my life.
But...
a lifetime is so long.
What if I can't afford your salary?
Then you can buy me.
How about
a tael of silver?
One tael of silver?
Do you think it's expensive?
Then how about
a copper coin?
Deal.
Then it's a deal.
You have my word.
I would regret it for the rest of my life
if I missed you silly boy.
♫I said I miss you because of your name♫
♫I'll spend the rest of my life with you♫
♫I can't tell dreams apart♫
♫Let love continue after flowers bloom♫
♫I said I miss you, don't doubt me♫
♫You left traces in my life♫
♫I want to be with you♫
♫Spring comes and winter goes. Let love continue♫
♫I think the world can't hear♫
♫Before the leaves fall♫
♫Your looking back♫
♫Has warmed the winter♫
♫I think the world can't hear♫
♫The four seasons have been circulating for a thousand years♫
♫You whispered forever to me♫
I've been standing all day.
This belongs to my brother?
Xue likes it.
Lu Li!
Senior... Senior Bai Feng?
Why are you in my room?
Where's Lu Li?
Lu Li?
Isn't he in the cell?
He... he has been released?
Really? He's out?
She was actually trying to lure me into telling the truth.
Stupid woman.
[Imperial Cosmo Hall]
Senior, are you looking for me?
Did you send Liu Shao to Ao Hen?
Who told you that?
Someone saw
Liu Shao's shredded clothes in Ao Hen's territory.
She died?
It would be nice if she died.
But how did you
get involved with
that great demon, Ao Hen?
Senior Du,
don't be so nervous.
I just
made a simple deal with Ao Hen.
Besides,
how could ordinary poison
fool Captain Fang
and hurt the Lord?
The Brahma tree revived!
Coming.
The Brahma tree, which had withered for 10,000 years,
sprouted again.
It did sprout.
Could it be that the Demon King and Demon Queen have returned?
I don't know.
Did something big happen?
Water Hyacinths.
Is the Brahma tree
revived?
Let's welcome the return of the Mother of Trees.
I, the Demon King of Aquatic Demons, He Na,
welcome the return of the Mother of Trees.
The Mother of Trees?
We welcome the return of the Mother of Trees.
The Brahma tree was once born of love
and was nourished by love.
It had also perceived the hate between lovers
and died because of it.
Did
it bloom again now
because of their love?
He Na, that medicine...
Do you remember
what you said last night?
You don't remember?
This...
You still don't remember?
Did you not mean what you said
when you were drunk?
I don't remember.
Wait.
Just kidding.
Of course I remember.
For one copper coin,
I sold myself to you,
right?
No regrets ever.
Let's go
find He Na.
The tree has blossomed.
We should be able to make the antidote.
Let's go.
This is the only female flower in the tree.
Mr. Tai made this flower into the antidote.
With this antidote,
even the most vicious poison can be cured.
Thank you, Demon King.
Liu Shao.
I have something for you too.
Keep this pendant close to you.
Keep it close? This...
Just call my name
when you need me,
and I'll show up.
Okay.
Thank you.
That day will never come.
She will need it someday,
won't she?
Anyway, you can't keep it around you.
Fine.
Let's go.
Your Majesty,
why didn't you tell Liu Shao
that so-called pendant
was made by a lot of demon energy.
If I told her about that,
I would definitely expect something in return.
I'd rather not
say anything at all.
Mother of Trees,
what do you think?
Marquis Wuyang has been poisoned for seven days.
He's about to die.
Lu Li and Liu Shao left the Aquatic Demons yesterday.
I wonder what magic they used.
They disappeared as soon as they came out.
They could only go to the Mansion anyway.
Now the Marquis Wuyang
has been unable to recover.
[Qiutian Pavilion]
Even if they go back,
the people who can protect Liu Shao are gone.
No, how could this happen?
My Lord!
My Lord.
[Qiutian Pavilion]
Chong,
don't tell anyone about the death of the Lord.
I'll discuss with you tomorrow.
From tomorrow onwards,
I'll be the new Marquis Wuyang.
This lord of the human world...
Who's there?
Chong.
My Lord.
Chong, why did you poison me?
How could I ever poison you?
Liar!
The King Herb is not poisonous.
It was you who poisoned me and set up Lu Li and Liu Shao, right?
Are you a human or a ghost?
You've poisoned me,
and I will not let you go no matter what happens.
My Lord,
do you remember the gift you gave me
when you take me as your disciple?
It doesn't matter.
Let's talk about your poisoning.
Back then, the gift you gave me
was this Qingfeng Sword.
Xue, run!
I got caught.
Tell me，
why did you pretend to be a ghost to scare me?
How did you imitate the Lord's voice?
I'm not good at anything else,
but I was pretty good at imitating people's voices
when I was a kid.
What about
this pretending to be ghosts?
We want to avenge Liu Shao and Lu Li.
You two idiots
are looking for revenge?
Go on.
If anything goes wrong,
you might end up like Liu Shao.
Senior Du.
Please spare my life.
I was talking nonsense.
I definitely didn't see you
poison the teacup.
It's true, Senior Du.
You are so stupid.
Why did you say that?
How did you see it?
Did you tell anyone else?
No.
I only told Xue.
Please spare my life, Senior Du.
I won't tell anyone.
Fine.
You can now go to hell
and accompany that dead man.
The Lord had been treated you so well.
Why did you still poison him,
and frame Liu Shao and Lu Li?
Treat me well?
If my father hadn't died
for saving him,
he wouldn't have treated me fairly.
And if my father didn't die,
the Marquis Wuyang should be him.
And my dad would have passed the throne to me long ago.
But there came Lu Li,
an unreliable man.
In the end,
he totally forgot about my existance.
How could he be so ungrateful?
The way I poisoned him and let him die with dignity,
is how I pay him back.
Go to hell!
Brother!
-My Lord! -My Lord!
Liu Shao.
[Imperial Cosmo Hall]
Don't look at me like that. That's right.
I set this all up.
After Liu Shao and I found the antidote,
we persuaded the Lord to take it and pretend to be dead.
If something happens to the Lord,
the next Marquis Wuyang will be you.
Then I asked Wang Jian and Xue
to act in front of you.
You would not be so vigilant
when they were exposed to you.
You've failed.
You have got complacent and forgetful.
Senior Du.
How could you make such mistake?
My Lord,
I'm innocent.
You raised me up.
I did it on impulse.
My Lord,
please forgive me.
Take him to the cell.
I'll interrogate him myself.
Guards!
My Lord.
-My Lord. -Go.
Please spare me this time.
My Lord, you raised me up.
My Lord!
You said
you treated me as your own son.
My Lord!
I will reward
the rest of you.
-Thank you, My Lord. -Thank you, My Lord.
Xue,
don't you think my performance,
acting skills, and lines
were all amazing?
And my belly
was
really doing a great job.
-So funny. -Brother.
Don't you think
you should treat me to a roast leg of lamb?
It's in your nature to be stupid.
You don't have to act at all.
Those lines were so long.
Come on.
You forgot all the lines in the middle.
It was me who reminded you.
-There's one more person. -What I did with the script...
was so good.
I know.
Alright.
I will go find her with you.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Wait.
What are you in such a hurry for?
I heard that the Lord is awake.
Lu Li and Liu Shao's suspicions were cleared.
They are back now.
What?
That's great.
I bet you must think
that I have already been tortured
to death, right?
I will avenge myself.
Let's have a fair battle.
You're asking for death?
Considering what you've done,
I should be crueler to you.
For Lu Li's sake
this time,
I'll spare you.
Lu Li.
Are you going to watch her
treat me like this?
Lu Li.
Senior.
This is the last time I will call you that.
Lu Li.
Are you doing this to me
because of an outsider?
First,
Liu Shao is not an outsider.
She is someone I care about.
Second,
I'm doing this because you've gone mad.
You are no longer the senior I knew.
Third,
were you involved in the poisoning of Marquis Wuyang or not?
The Lord
still needs an explanation from you.
I...
Today I will sever ties with you.
From now on, you are not my senior anymore.
[Imperial Cosmo Hall]
Are you telling the truth?
Did Bai Feng instigate you to do it?
My Lord,
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have listened to Bai Feng's instigation.
She gave me the poison.
She must have colluded with the demon world.
My Lord.
I didn't realize my mistake at the time.
For my father's sake,
please forgive me.
Bai Feng,
did you hear it?
Is it true?
Can Senior Du be exempt from punishment
by saying that?
Then take it as my own idea.
I am willing to be punished
if I can help Senior Du by doing so.
What do you mean by "take it as"?
It was all your idea.
It seems that the fire in the Pearl Pavilion
was also set by you.
I didn't expect a demon fire
to appear in my mansion.
Did you use
some kind of demonic stuff?
Fang Zhan!
Search!
My Lord.
You don't have to do that.
It was all my idea.
I was the one who got Senior Du involved.
Please forgive him.
My Lord.
How did you get
Ao Hen's Spirit Devouring Orb?
Did you conspire with Ao Hen
to harm me?
How could this be?
It belongs to Bai Feng.
I didn't collude with Ao Hen.
Absolutely not.
Senior Du,
I've already confessed.
What else do you want me to do?
It's a serious crime
to collude with demons.
Senior Du, do you want me to die?
It's not true, My Lord.
Trust me.
It's not true.
These were really Bai Feng's ideas.
She...
she colluded with Ao Hen
in order to kill Lu Li and Liu Shao.
She even urged me to poison you.
The Spirit Devouring Orb.
The Spirit Devouring Orb also belongs to her.
What good is it to me
if they die?
Senior,
you are the Lord's real disciple.
Lu Li is your enemy, not mine.
I swear!
I will spare your life
if you can take ten moves from me.
My Lord,
are you trying to kill him?
Shut up!
No, no.
I am not capable of doing so.
If it was Lu Li now,
he would definitely dare to fight against me
no matter what would happen.
But you don't
even have the courage to fight me.
How could I have such a disciple as you?
Lu Li.
You are mentioning him again.
My Lord.
Have you ever cared about me?
You don't deserve it
right now.
It was you...
You vicious woman did this to me.
Senior Du!
It's all my fault.
Du Mingchong
colluded with demons
and did these vicious things.
Therefore, I will abolish his cultivation
and
expel him.
From now on,
he is no longer a member
here.
Yes.
Senior Du.
My Lord,
what about Bai Feng?
She lost her mind
and did wrong things.
At this moment,
she should have realized her mistake.
Take her back to Lingxi Yard
and ground her for a month.
Then demote her to an ordinary disciple.
You're moving out tomorrow?
I'll be lonely.
Do you still think you are our senior?
From now on,
it will be Liu Shao's room.
Quickly pick up your things and follow me.
You shouldn't have done this.
Let's go.
Liu Shao.
Let's just wait and see.
The Moon Sword
has been silent in the human world for thousands of years.
No matter how hard people tried,
no one could pull out this sword.
You can refine the remaining King Herb
to prolong your lifespan,
and continue to train disciples and select talents.
Fang Zhan,
do you know the reason why
I want the King Herb?
Live forever and protect the world forever.
No.
It's because
I'm also afraid of death.
But I've figured it out now.
Using King Herb
to bring a hope to the human world
is better than keeping myself alive for another ten years.
The Moon Sword
was once the weapon of God of the Moonlight.
I heard that it can split mountains, cut off the sea
and kill all demons.
If any of my disciples pulls out this sword,
it will definitely be a blessing
to all living beings in the human world.
Let all the disciples
gather in front of the Moon Stone tomorrow.
We will start the ultimate trial.
I
will choose an heir myself.
[Lingyun Residence]
The left side?
This is the left side.
The left side.
The right side is better.
Xue will like the pattern
and the color.
That's it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm sure.
I'm so tired.
My...
All right.
This side.
Okay, this side.
And that side.
Are you feeling better?
The guards hired by others are just to help them fight.
Not only do I have to buy you sheets as your guard,
but I also have to deliver them to you.
If I had known earlier,
I would not have given you the recording stone.
I have given you a massage.
Why are you still saying this?
You still have to help me with the sheets.
Miss Liu,
don't you think you are too greedy?
I...
Are you sure you don't want to see your bill?
You owe me a lot.
Really?
Then,
can I refuse to pay?
You can't do that.
Just tell me if it's okay.
How can I say no?
Lu Li,
when we pull out the Moon Sword
and defeat Ao Hen,
remember to ask your master to come to my house to propose marriage.
I warned you not to fall in love with Liu Shao.
What you're doing is not good for either of you.
Lu Li,
my suppression of Soul-Devouring Spell is only temporarily effective.
If you are seriously injured,
or the caster activates the spell to break through my suppression,
the backlash will make you die faster.
Hey.
You are not willing to do that?
How is that possible?
First of all,
we have to pull out
the Moon Sword that no one could pull out, right?
Tomorrow is the ultimate trial.
Just wait and see how skilled I am.
I once said
that I would reward those
who retrieve the immortal grass.
Today,
I will give you the opportunity
of this ultimate trial.
Liu Shao, Lu Li.
Are you ready?
-Yes. -I'm ready.
The person who passes the ultimate trial
will not only become my heir,
but also be possible to pull out the Moon Sword
and become its master.
Let's begin.
Go in.
It seems that the trial at the Moon Stone has begun.
What's wrong, brother?
Are you still thinking about that Immortal Ze Shui?
She is not Immortal Ze Shui.
Since she's not,
why can't you forget about her?
You even
gave her a pendant,
and promised to help her at any time.
Fu,
stop spying on my whereabouts.
You may not know it,
but the ultimate trial of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
is very occult.
It's said
that as long as you take a wrong step in the illusion of Moon Stone,
you will never be able to come out again.
Do you think your little fairy
will have a chance to get out?
Liu Shao?